isprime.com 2010-01-22

# ISPrime - Privacy Policy

> **Online Privacy Statement**
> 
>   
>  **I. General**  
> 
> 
> ISPrime respects the privacy of every individual who visits our Web sites, responds to our interactive advertisements or sends us e-mail. This Privacy Statement outlines the information ISPrime will collect and how we will use that information. This Statement will also instruct you on what to do if you do not want your personal information collected or shared when you visit ISPrime Web sites, respond to our Web-based advertisements or send us email. 
> 
> **II. Security**  
> 
> 
> All order forms on ISPrime.com utilize a Secure Socket Layer (SSL) or Secure Electronic Transaction (SET) protocol to provide "secure sessions" for our visitors. Through the "secure session," information that you input into a ISPrime.com order form will be sent and will arrive privately and unaltered at a ISPrime server. This security prohibits other companies and Web users from being able to access your information.
> 
> **III. Personally-Identifiable Information**  
> 
> 
> ISPrime will not collect any personally-identifiable information about you (that is, your name, address, telephone number, or email address) unless you provide it to us voluntarily.
> 
> The following are some examples of when ISPrime may require that you provide personally-identifiable information: 
> 
>   * to complete an online order for a product or service (if you do not wish to complete an online order form, we will always provide an option for you to complete an order by calling a toll free phone number) 
>   * to enter an online contest or sweepstakes (if you do not wish to complete an online contest or sweepstakes form, we will always provide an option for you to enter by mailing a 3 x 5 card to a specific address) 
>   * to request more information about new or current ISPrime, ISPrime or ISPrime products or services If you do not want your personally-identifiable information collected, please do not submit it to us. If you have already submitted this information and would like for us to remove it from our records, please contact us at the email address listed at the bottom of this Statement. We will use reasonable efforts to delete your information from our existing files. 
> 

> 
> When you do provide us with personally-identifiable information, we may use that information in the following ways, unless stated otherwise: 
> 
>   * we may store and process that information to better understand all customer needs and how we can improve our products and services for all customers 
>   * we may use that information to contact you with new promotions and announcements if you have previously provided your permission and if the promotions and announcements are in your interest 
>   * we may contact you if we have questions about your account ISPrime will not sell personally-identifiable information to third parties, unless stated at the time of collection. We may share information with business partners. We are committed to giving you the choice whether or not we use your information for marketing purposes or share information with business partners. 
> 

> 
> **IV. Children**  
> 
> 
> ISPrime has no intention of collecting any personally-identifiable information (that is, name, address, telephone number, or email address) from individuals under 18 years of age. Where appropriate, ISPrime will specifically instruct children not to submit such information on our Web sites or advertisements without consent of a parent or guardian. If a child has provided us with personally-identifiable information without the consent of a parent or guardian, a parent or guardian of that child should contact us at the email address listed at the bottom of this Statement if they would like this information deleted from our records. We will use reasonable efforts to delete the child's information from our existing files.
> 
> **V. Non-Personally-Identifiable Information Collected Automatically**  
> 
> 
> In some cases, we may collect information about you that is not personally-identifiable. Examples of this type of information include the type of Internet Browser you are using, the type of computer operating system you are using, and the domain name of the Web site and/or Internet Service Provider from which you linked to our site or advertisement.
> 
> Similar to personally identifiable information, we will not sell non-personally-identifiable information to third parties, unless stated at the time of collection. We may share non-personally identifiable information with business partners.
> 
> **VI. Use of Cookies**  
> 
> 
> When you view one of our Web sites or advertisements, we may store some information on your computer. This information will be in the form of a "Cookie" or similar file and will be used to determine ways to improve our Web sites, advertisements, products or services. For example, Cookies allow us to tailor a Web site to better match your interests and preferences. With most Internet Browsers, you can erase Cookies from your computer hard drive, block all Cookies, or receive a warning before a Cookie is stored. Please refer to your Browser instructions or help screen to learn more about these functions.
> 
> **VII. Declining Email Offers**  
> 
> 
> As outlined in Section III. of this Statement, we will only send email promotions or announcements to you if you have previously provided your permission for us to do so via the ordering process or via our Email subscription center. Although many customers tell us they appreciate receiving notice of these carefully designed promotions and announcements, we recognize the importance of providing you with choices. If you have signed up via our subscription center, you may unsubscribe by filling out our simple online unsubscription form. If you are an existing customer that opted in to receive notices from ISPrime and would like to be opted out from future notifications, please see section VIII on Who to contact.
> 
> **VIII. Who to Contact**  
> 
> 
> If you have submitted personally-identifiable information through a ISPrime Web site or interactive advertisement, and would like that information deleted from our records, please contact us at our email address, support@isprime.com. We will use reasonable efforts to delete this information from our existing files.
